Adarsh Parikh

Pursuing CAPM® | Pursuing PSM® |Ex-Project Coordinator at Royal Enfield +1-647-333-3369|parikhadarsh10@gmail.com Product Analyst Intern – SOTI Inc.

Summary

I am a quality-oriented professional with a demonstrated ability to lead projects and a successful trackrecord working with key internal and external stakeholders to develop new products. As a Regional Project Coordinator, I worked on projects and was responsible for conducting customer andmarket analysis, developing, managing, and maintaining data from the stakeholders, doing an internal risk management analysis, and ensuring deliverables were completed on time. Moreover, I was also responsible for defining the project vision and drive critical business decisions for our developer markets.

I am a well-rounded professional with solid communication (written and verbal), organizational and interpersonal skills. My experience has helped me in building excellent writing skills and has also taught me the ability to multitask and perform activities with minimal supervision. I have good attention to detail, and I work the best in a cross-functional team for managing tasks and priorities. I am an award-winning customer service executive with a prime focus on customer success.

Skills Knowledge

- Project leading and managing skills- Led 12 small size projects in a span of 1 year 8 months
- Project Management Tools- Jira, MS Project, Kanban, Primavera, MS Visio
- Data Visualization and Analytical Tools: Power BI, Advanced Excel(vlookup, macros, pivot)
- Other basic tools- Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
- Pursuing CAPM (Certified Associate in Project Management)
- Pursuing PSM I (Professional Scrum Master) Scrum.org
- Learning Jira Software April 2021
- Learning MS Project, Sharepoint- Jan 2021
- Learning Tableau Jan 2021
- Effective Communication, Time Management

- Strategic Problem Solving
- Conflict Resolution
- Critical Thinking
- Effective Interpersonal Skills
- Multitasking

Experience

Regional Project Coordinator - Royal Enfield

Aug 2018 - Apr 2020

- Conducted process documentation, business case documentation, requirement analysis, collaboration with numerous teams and held meetings as needed.
- Have proactively managed reporting manager's travel arrangements and expenses, and managed department travel expense analysis against budget.
- Attended meetings and ensured minutes of meeting, action plans were clearly documented and communicated.
- Supported PMO and Delivery Teams with deliverables such as status reports, meeting notes, schedules, presentations, resource requests, risks, and issue

- tracking documents.
- Provided status updates of work in progress and support with project forecasting, business requirements documentation, cost control, and time efficiency program.
- Managed communication plans to ensure timely communication with various levels of internal stakeholders, external stakeholders and clients.
- Support projects/initiatives as assigned by the manager and have facilitated internal audits for the company promptly.

Lead Generator Trainee – Ashok Leyland

Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

- Generated 1000+ leads by meeting all the transport managers of the school.
- Efficiently did market research and marketing activities, created 1000+ customer enquiries database, email marketing, cold calling, and used digital marketing & social media for lead generation.
- Client Retention: Work closely with the customers and liaison for other issues, such as sales or marketing-related matters. Also, develop productive relationships with clients as necessary.
- Identified, contacted, pitched sales presentations, and helped sign highquality merchant partners.
- Develop a strong understanding of payments, lending, technology, business development.
- Obtained insights into customers' usage of current products, untapped opportunities, and buyer personas, through interviews, surveys, focus groups and sales data.

Education

Advanced Project Management and Strategic Leadership – Lambton College, Sept 2020 – April 2022

Bachelor's in Mechanical Engineering – Gujarat Technological University, India